#### Contact

nurseskippy@outlook.com

www.linkedin.com/in/shawnna-alred-685661107 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS)

**CCRN** 

# Shawnna Alred

MSN, MBA, RN, CCRN

Phoenix, Arizona Area

### Summary

Experienced Intensive Care Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Critical Care Nursing, Healthcare, and Patient Safety. Strong healthcare services professional with a Master's degree focused in Nursing Leadership and a Master's in Business Administration from Grand Canyon University.

## Experience

Phoenix Children's Hospital
Critical Care RN
June 2011 - Present (9 years 1 month)

St. Joseph's Hospital and Medical Center Critical Care RN January 2005 - June 2011 (6 years 6 months)

John C. Lincoln Deer Valley Hospital PCT November 2002 - December 2004 (2 years 2 months)

#### Education

Grand Canyon University

Master's degree, Nursing Leadership (2018 - 2019)

**Grand Canyon University** 

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Business, Management, Marketing, and healthcare  $\cdot$  (2017 - 2018)

**Grand Canyon University** 

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2000 - 2004)